<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Film Gallery</string>
    <string name="empty_message">No films to display!</string>
    <string name="favourites_on">Show all</string>
    <string name="favourites_off">Show favourites</string>
    <string name="search_on">Show all categories</string>
    <string name="search_off">Search by genre</string>
    <string name="search_title">Choose the genre</string>
    <string name="comedy">Comedy</string>
    <string name="action">Action</string>
    <string name="horror">Horror</string>
    <string name="description">Description</string>
    <string name="gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="actors">Actors</string>
    <string name="genre">Genre:</string>
    <string name="favourite_btn_desc">Favourite button</string>
    <string name="poster_desc">Movie poster</string>
    <string name="the_matrix_title">The Matrix</string>
    <string name="home_alone_title">Home Alone</string>
    <string name="iron_man_title">Iron Man</string>
    <string name="american_psycho_title">American Psycho</string>
    <string name="knives_out_title">Knives Out</string>
    <string name="once_upon_a_time_in_hollywood_title">Once Upon a Time in Hollywood</string>
    <string name="the_ring_title">The Ring</string>
    <string name="baby_driver_title">Baby Driver</string>
    <string name="the_matrix_description">Thomas A. Anderson is a man living two lives. By day he is an average computer programmer and by night a hacker known as Neo. Neo has always questioned his reality, but the truth is far beyond his imagination. Neo finds himself targeted by the police when he is contacted by Morpheus, a legendary computer hacker branded a terrorist by the government. As a rebel against the machines, Neo must confront the agents: super-powerful computer programs devoted to stopping Neo and the entire human rebellion.</string>
    <string name="home_alone_description">It is Christmas time and the McCallister family is preparing for a vacation in Paris, France. But the youngest in the family, Kevin (Macaulay Culkin), got into a scuffle with his older brother Buzz (Devin Ratray) and was sent to his room, which is on the third floor of his house. Then, the next morning, while the rest of the family was in a rush to make it to the airport on time, they completely forgot about Kevin, who now has the house all to himself. Being home alone was fun for Kevin, having a pizza all to himself, jumping on his parents\' bed, and making a mess. Then, Kevin discovers about two burglars, Harry (Joe Pesci) and Marv (Daniel Stern), about to rob his house on Christmas Eve. Kevin acts quickly by wiring his own house with makeshift booby traps to stop the burglars and to bring them to justice.</string>
    <string name="iron_man_description">Tony Stark. Genius, billionaire, playboy, philanthropist. Son of legendary inventor and weapons contractor Howard Stark. When Tony Stark is assigned to give a weapons presentation to an Iraqi unit led by Lt. Col. James Rhodes, he\'s given a ride on enemy lines. That ride ends badly when Stark\'s Humvee that he\'s riding in is attacked by enemy combatants. He survives - barely - with a chest full of shrapnel and a car battery attached to his heart. In order to survive he comes up with a way to miniaturize the battery and figures out that the battery can power something else. Thus Iron Man is born. He uses the primitive device to escape from the cave in Iraq. Once back home, he then begins work on perfecting the Iron Man suit. But the man who was put in charge of Stark Industries has plans of his own to take over Tony\'s technology for other matters.</string>
    <string name="american_psycho_description">It\'s the late 1980s. Twenty-seven year old Wall Streeter Patrick Bateman travels among a closed network of the proverbial beautiful people, that closed network in only they able to allow others like themselves in a feeling of superiority. Patrick has a routinized morning regimen to maintain his appearance of attractiveness and fitness. He, like those in his network, are vain, narcissistic, egomaniacal and competitive, always having to one up everyone else in that presentation of oneself, but he, unlike the others, realizes that, for himself, all of these are masks to hide what is truly underneath, someone/something inhuman in nature. In other words, he is comprised of a shell resembling a human that contains only greed and disgust, greed in wanting what others may have, and disgust for those who do not meet his expectations and for himself in not being the first or the best.</string>
    <string name="knives_out_description">When renowned crime novelist Harlan Thrombey (Christopher Plummer) is found dead at his estate just after his 85th birthday, the inquisitive and debonair Detective Benoit Blanc (Daniel Craig) is mysteriously enlisted to investigate. From Harlan\'s disfunctional family to his devoted staff, Blanc sifts through a web of red herrings and self-serving lies to uncover the truth behind Harlan\'s untimely death.</string>
    <string name="once_upon_a_time_in_hollywood_description">Quentin Tarantino\'s Once Upon a Time… in Hollywood visits 1969 Los Angeles, where everything is changing, as TV star Rick Dalton (Leonardo DiCaprio) and his longtime stunt double Cliff Booth (Brad Pitt) make their way around an industry they hardly recognize anymore. The ninth film from the writer-director features a large ensemble cast and multiple storylines in a tribute to the final moments of Hollywood\'s golden age.</string>
    <string name="the_ring_description">Rachel Keller is a journalist investigating a videotape that may have killed four teenagers (including her niece). There is an urban legend about this tape: the viewer will die seven days after watching it. If the legend is correct, Rachel will have to run against time to save her son\'s and her own life.</string>
    <string name="baby_driver_description">Baby is a young and partially hearing impaired getaway driver who can make any wild move while in motion with the right track playing. It\'s a critical talent he needs to survive his indentured servitude to the crime boss, Doc, who values his role in his meticulously planned robberies. However, just when Baby thinks he is finally free and clear to have his own life with his new girlfriend, Debora, Doc coerces him back for another job. Now saddled with a crew of thugs too violently unstable to keep to Doc\'s plans, Baby finds himself and everything he cares for in terrible danger. To survive and escape the coming maelstrom, it will take all of Baby\'s skill, wits and daring, but even on the best track, can he make it when life is forcing him to face the music?</string>
    <string name="actor_1">Keanu Reeves</string>
    <string name="actor_2">Macaulay Culkin</string>
    <string name="actor_3">Robert Downey Jr.</string>
    <string name="actor_4">Christian Bale</string>
    <string name="actor_5">Daniel Craig</string>
    <string name="actor_6">Leonardo DiCaprio</string>
    <string name="actor_7">Naomi Watts</string>
    <string name="actor_8">Ansel Elgort</string>
    <string name="actor_image_content">Actor image</string>
    <string name="actors_empty_message">No actors to display!</string>
    <string name="gallery_empty_message">No photos to display!</string>
    <string name="gallery_img_desc">Photo from the movie</string>
</resources>
